{
	"1":{
		"id": "1",
		"prompt": "If each lightbulb is a bit of information, what is the maximum amount of data that can be conveyed in a message by the lights on the stage?",
		"options": {
			"0": "8 Nibbles",
			"1": "32 Bits",
			"2": "128 Bits",
			"3": "8 Bytes"
		},
		"answer": "3"	
	},
	"2":{
		"id": "2",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 10 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "ü©∏",
			"1": "üòÇ",
			"2": "‚ù§",
			"3": "üí°"
		},
		"answer": "2"	
	},
	"3":{
		"id": "3",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 7 Cyber Security in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "HI DADS",
			"1": "HI MOMS",
			"2": "SEGFAULT",
			"3": "BE SAFE"
		},
		"answer": "1"	
	},
	"4":{
		"id": "4",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 3 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "DPSSFDU",
			"1": "QUACK",
			"2": "ENHANCE",
			"3": "CORRECT"
		},
		"answer": "0"	
	},
	"5":{
		"id": "5",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 9 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "</html>",
			"1": "hello.py",
			"2": "<html>",
			"3": "ENHANCE"
		},
		"answer": "0"	
	},
	"6":{
		"id": "6",
		"prompt": "What does the hidden message under this website's logo translate to",
		"options": {
			"0": "THIS IS CS50",
			"1": "CS50 LIGHTS",
			"2": "HI CS50",
			"3": "CS50 RULES"
		},
		"answer": "1"	
	},
	"7":{
		"id": "7",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 0 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "CORRECT",
			"1": "CAT CAT",
			"2": "SCRATCH",
			"3": "HI MOM"
		},
		"answer": "3"	
	},
	"8":{
		"id": "8",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 6 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "</html>",
			"1": "hello.py",
			"2": "<html>",
			"3": "ENHANCE"
		},
		"answer": "1"	
	},
	"9":{
		"id": "9",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 2 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "HI MOM",
			"1": "DUCK",
			"2": "QUACK",
			"3": "DPSSFDU"
		},
		"answer": "2"	
	},
	"10":{
		"id": "10",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 7 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "BOOOOO",
			"1": "SEGFAULT",
			"2": "HI MOMS",
			"3": "BOOOOOOO"
		},
		"answer": "3"	
	},
	"11":{
		"id": "11",
		"prompt": "How many light bulbs are there on the stage of CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "42",
			"1": "69",
			"2": "64",
			"3": "60"
		},
		"answer": "2"	
	},
	"12":{
		"id": "12",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 1 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "CORRECT",
			"1": "DPSSFDU",
			"2": "SEGFAULT",
			"3": "ENHANCE"
		},
		"answer": "0"	
	},
	"13":{
		"id": "13",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 5 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "CORRECT",
			"1": "DPSSFDU",
			"2": "SEGFAULT",
			"3": "ENHANCE"
		},
		"answer": "2"	
	},
	"14":{
		"id": "14",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 8 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "</html>",
			"1": "hello.py",
			"2": "<html>",
			"3": "ENHANCE"
		},
		"answer": "2"	
	},
	"15":{
		"id": "15",
		"prompt": "What is the hidden message of week 4 in CS50 2021?",
		"options": {
			"0": "DPSSFDU",
			"1": "QUACK",
			"2": "ENHANCE",
			"3": "CORRECT"
		},
		"answer": "2"	
	}
}